Anna Grace Conover

I am an outgoing person who knows how to talk to people, and I like helping the people I talk to! I learn fast, take pride in getting my work done, and I enjoy challenges. I have worked seven years in customer service, and thus am very confident with all different kinds of customers.

Experience

Potholder Café

November 2019- Present

Server

Responsible for knowledge of menu and customer experience. Knowledge of ordering systems and payment machines. Duties include food/drink running, placing orders, and preparing tables.

Brilliant Earth

March 2018 – November 2019

Customer Experience Receptionist

Responsible for inventory and back of house operations, as well as checking in guests and assisting sales representatives with knowledge and items.

Museum of Ice Cream

October 2017 – December 2017

Front of House

Was responsible for creating a fun, informative experience for each guest. Shared relevant facts about the product while creating a connection with each guest.

BJ's Restaurant and Brewhouse

September 2015 – April 2016

Host/Server

As Host was responsible for welcoming guests, answering phones, coordinating tables, and seating guests. Won an award for customer service due to customer comments and manager observation. Became a server and was responsible for knowing the menu and giving guests exceptional service.

Education

University of Oklahoma

2016

Bachelor of Fine Arts: Drama

UCLA Extension Coding Bootcamp

2020

Certificate of Completion

Portfolio: annaxgrace.github.io/Portfolio anna.grace.conover@gmail.com